{
    "id": "42280f6f9b444aec8ef2fb1e655e93a1",
    "title": "Both, Either, Neither",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ".................. of us were ill, so we didn't go to school.",
            "description": "Both means first as well as the second.",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": ".................. of these answers is correct.",
            "description": "Both would be correct here if the verb was are.  ",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Both",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": ".................. my parents are teachers.",
            "description": "Both means first as well as the second.",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She kissed them ................... on the forehead.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................... my children like sports.",
            "description": "Both means first as well as the second. ",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn't like .................... of these.",
            "description": "Either means one or the other. ",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Both",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't choose between them. I like them ....................",
            "description": "Both means first as well as second.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................... Sam nor Peter turned up today.",
            "description": "Neither means none of the two.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Either",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't like .................. of them.",
            "description": "Neither means one of the two. ",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... him nor his parents were able to give a satisfactory explanation.",
            "description": "Neither means none of the two.",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited ................... of them.",
            "description": "Both means first as well as second.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I wrote to ................... of them but .................. replied.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both, neither",
                "either, both",
                "either, neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}